

About Me

I am a passionate content strategist with over seven years' experience in developing content and communications strategies.

I take pride in my editorial, design, and collaboration skills

Areas of Proficiency

- · Adobe Suite
- Copywriting
- UX Design
- SEO
- Social Strategy
- Brand Management

(678)983-9093



Atlanta, GA 30067



ale.smith90@gmail.com

Alex Smith

(678)983-9093 | ale.smith90@gmail.com | alesmith.contently.com | linkedin.com/in/alexsmith90

EXPERIENCE

Digital Content Supervisor UPS Capital 2018 - Present

Increased traffic to upscapital.com by

- · Maintaining social media channels, strategy, content, and assets
- Preparing an editorial calendar and creating needed content
 - case studies, blog posts, website copy, emails, and videos
- Execute content marketing strategy across the entire buyer's journey

Content Specialist

UPS Capital 2014 - 2018

Improved employee engagement scores by

- Writing internal communications memos, updates, blog posts, etc
- · Publishing and distributing content to relevant users
 - Content included written posts, videos, photos, and graphics
- Regularly auditing content to ensure material is current

Freelance Multimedia Journalist

WSAV-TV 2013 - 2014

- · Write copy for nightly broadcasts
- · Script, film, and edit video for news segments

EDUCATION

B.A in Multimedia Communications

Georgia Southern University, Statesboro, GA 2009-2013

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Analytics

Online Certification Google 2017

UI/UX

6 month bootcamp Georgia Tech 2020-2021

Adobe After Effects

5 day bootcamp Ledet Training 2018